# Slava Trofimov

### **Senior Front End Developer**

Richmond Hill, ON L4C 1E5 slava@trofimov.ca +1 289 980 8683

I'm working in the web development industry for more than 12 years and am familiar with all aspects of a website/app development cycle, from initial analysis and planning, creating wireframes to production deployment.

I have strong JavaScript, Vue.js, REST, CSS/SCSS, and HTML5 skills. For the last several years I've gained wide experience with Laravel and PHP in general and worked on many Laravel+Vue.js/Nuxt.js projects as a Lead developer.

Have wide experience with MySQL, WordPress, Opencart, and Electron.js.

I feel confident working with technologies like Git, Docker, Figma, Jira / ClickUp, Slack, etc.

Always seeking skill improvement and better practices.

## Work Experience

#### **Senior Front End Developer**

Codepxl - Toronto, ON January 2019 to Present

Toronto-based App development, website design, complex system development, and graphic design agency. Vue3/Nuxt3, SPA, Laravel, Electron, WordPress.

#### **Front End Developer**

EvolutionInDesignZ - Toronto, ON May 2018 to December 2018

Web app development, graphic design, and online marketing agency. HTML5, SCSS, SPA, Laravel + Vue.js, Opencart, WordPress

#### **Front End Developer**

Electrolight Enterprises - Toronto, ON August 2017 to May 2018

Lighting & Design Services for the GTA. Corporate website maintenance. HTML5 / JS / SCSS / PHP, etc.

#### Front End Developer

iMoan.ru - Moscow August 2015 to July 2017

One of the fast-growing e-commerce projects in the adult industry. HTML5 (PUG) / CSS3 (SCSS) / JS(jQuery, Angular) / Opencart, Web/UI design, VPS administrative, SEO, project menagment, work with remote employees.

### **Lead Front End Developer**

Web Solution Ltd. - Moscow March 2013 to August 2015

Web design studio with hundreds of clients. Front-end development and UI design. HTML5 (PUG) /CSS (LESS) / JS (jQuery) / Joomla, WordPress, Opencart.

### Front End Developer

Giftery corp. - Moscow February 2012 to March 2013

Startup Giftery.ru is a buyer's bonus card system with many commerce partners. Front-end development. HTML5 / CSS3 / JS (jQuery)

### **Front End Developer**

Predestination.ru - Moscow January 2011 to February 2012

Popular business training project with multiple courses and programs. Front-end development, Web design, UI Design. HTML / CSS / JS (jQuery) / WordPress

### **Junior Front End Developer**

KM ONLINE, R-STYLE COMPANY GROUP - Moscow 2008 to 2010

News, entertainment, and media. Work on social media project - vkrugudruzei.ru. Front-end development. HTML / CSS / JS (jQuery)

## Education

### **Master in Computer Science**

Moscow State Open University - Moscow 2007 to 2008

#### **Diploma in Computer Science**

Moscow Technological University - Moscow 2003 to 2007

#### Skills

- JavaScript (7 years)
- Vue.js (5 years)
- Laravel (4 years)
- CSS (10+ years)
- SASS (5 years)
- PHP (5 years)
- MySQL (5 years)
- Node.js (3 years)
- HTML5 (10+ years)

- GitHub (6 years)
- Bootstrap (5 years)
- TailwindCss (3 years)
- Docker (4 years)
- jQuery (7 years)
- Nuxt.js (3 years)
- Responsive styling (8 years)
- REST (6 years)
- TypeScript (2 years)

# Languages

- English Fluent
- Russian Expert

## Links

https://github.com/pmbstyle

https://trofimov.ca

https://www.linkedin.com/in/slava-trofimov-ca